### **CURRICULUM VITAE**

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION

Name: MOHAMMAD REZZA DANIAL BIN MD AMIR

**Age:** 24

Date of Birth: 14 MAY 1995

Address: Bandar Utama, Damansara, Selangor

Mobile: 017 482 5310

Email: rezzadanialcs@gmail.com

Website: rezzadanial.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/rezzadanial



#### **PROFILE**

I am **all rounded** young professional intending to continue my career development as an **UI/UX Designer.** I think in term of results and objectives, I am **workaholic**, and I work with decisiveness and full with passion. **Keen learner** with any new technology. **Fast learner** and able to find **resources** and **solution** on the Internet. Even though I just 24 years old, I have a lot of **professional experience** in many fields. I was trained to work under pressure and long working hours. In term of social life, I am a friendly and fun person.

# **EDUCATION**

MAC 2016 – JULY 2018	Bachelor Degree in Netcentric Computing		
UNIVERSITI TEKNOLOGI MARA	<ul> <li>MARA Technology University, Shah Alam</li> <li>Major in Web Development and Computer Networking</li> <li>Relevant Courses: CCNA, Web Technologies and Networking</li> <li>Final Year Project: Unifying Crowdsourcing Platform using         Ruby on Rails     </li> <li>CGPA: 3.28</li> </ul>		
JUN 2013 – NOVEMBER 2015	Diploma in Computer Science		
UNIVERSITI TEKNOLOGI MARA	<ul> <li>MARA Technology University, Perlis</li> <li>Learnt general and fundamentals of all computer science branches</li> <li>Relevant Courses: Object Oriented Programming, Multimedia, Data Communication, Operating System</li> <li>CGPA: 3.06</li> </ul>		
2011 – 2012	Sijil Pelajaran Malaysia (SPM)		
TO ASAS KENAJUM	<ul> <li>Sekolah Menengah Sains Tun Syed Sheh Shahabudin</li> <li>Science and ICT stream</li> <li>SPM: 5A, 3B, 2C</li> </ul>		

# **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES**

AUGUST 2018 - PRESENT	Business Integration Arch Analyst at Accenture	
accenture	<ul> <li>Develop and Debug Web Application that built using Angular and Spring Boot</li> <li>Software Testing for large scale and complex web portal that integrated with many subsystem</li> <li>Conduct a User Acceptance Test session with client</li> <li>Learn about Integration testing tools like SOAP UI and Postman</li> <li>Familiar with JIRA application to keep track defects issues</li> </ul>	
JUNE - OCTOBER 2018	Software Developer at Linear DMS Sdn. Bhd	
COMS .	<ul> <li>Sains@USM, CREST Place Block A, 1st Floor, No.10, Persiaran Bukit Jambul, Bayan Lepas, Penang</li> <li>Rapid Prototyping using Sketch and Adobe XD</li> <li>Participate in SDLC focusing on UI/UX, coding and debugging.</li> <li>Collaborate with Back-end developers to integrate userfacing elements with server-side logic.</li> <li>Create original graphic design.</li> <li>Identify and troubleshoot UX problems.</li> <li>Create Real-Time Data Visualization with D3.js library and SVG for Real-Time Location System's sensor.</li> </ul>	

FEBRUARY 2018 – JUNE 2018	Intern at Novatis Resources Sdn. Bhd.	
novatis (resources	<ul> <li>CDB Perdana 2, Persiaran Flora Cyber 12, Cyberjaya</li> <li>Assist Engineer during Data Center maintenance.</li> <li>Learn about Servers Virtualization, Networks         Equipment, Storage and Backups and Tape.</li> <li>Familiar with servers from IBM, HP, DELL, and Lenovo.</li> <li>Provide technical drawing for client's documentation.</li> <li>Web Development using Angular.Js</li> </ul>	
MAY 2016 – PRESENT	Trainer under Malaysia Digital Economy Cooperation (MDEC)	
Driving Transformation	<ul> <li>Consult and train a local citizen about government digital economy programme.</li> <li>Facilitate them to earn side income from doing online jobs.</li> <li>Conduct a presentation at organizations about Digital Economy.</li> </ul>	
JUNE 2014 – OCTOBER 2015	Instructor Assistant	
UNIVERSITI TEKNOLOGI MARA	<ul> <li>MARA Technology University, Perlis</li> <li>Assist the Instructor during Co-Curriculum activities such as rope climbing, abseiling, marching, first aid course.</li> <li>Plan and manage co-curriculum course for approximately 2000 students each semester.</li> <li>Manage the student's files and attendance.</li> </ul>	

#### **TECHNICAL CERTIFICATIONS**



## **CyberSecurity Fundamentals Exam (CSX)**

- License number: 2017-1098939-CSXF
- Covered all fundamental aspect of Cyber Security in an Organization.
- Risk Assessment
- Network Security



# **Certified IP Associate (CIPA)**

- License number: CIPA.1503422
- Covered deep Internet Protocol course.
- IP Configuration and Design
- Network Monitoring

#### **TECHNICAL COURSE**



## **Server Infrastructure Penetration Testing**

- Hands on training in Penetration Testing
- Learn Ethical Hacking
- Port Scanning
- Linux Security/Hacking Tools



### **IT Project Management: Crash-Course**

- Risk Assessment
- Gantt Chart
- Funding
- Team Management

All certificates can be view in my LinkedIn Profile.

### **HONOUR AND ACHIEVEMENT**

	Young Lieutenant (Kesatria)
UNIVERSITI TEKNOLOGI MARA	<ul> <li>Commissioned as Young Officer for Kesatria uniform body.</li> </ul>
	DEAN AWARD
UNIVERSITI TEKNOLOGI MARA	Awarded for Excellent Result in Academic
WELTERBE.	MOUNT KINABALU EXPEDITION
AIGNOW THE PATRIMOUNT OF THE P	Has successfully climbed Mount Kinabalu summit at 13,435 feet from sea level.

All certificates can be view in my LinkedIn Profile.

## **LANGUAGES**

•	Bahasa Malaysia		
	○ Written: Excellent		

o **Spoken:** Excellent

o **Reading:** Excellent

## English

o Written: Excellent

o **Spoken:** Excellent

o **Reading:** Excellent

### **MAJOR SKILLS**

SKILL	PROFECIENCY	DESCRIPTIONS
UI/UX Design  Web  Development	Advanced	<ul> <li>UI/UX design using Sketch, Adobe XD and Invision.</li> <li>Prototyping and Wire framing</li> <li>Logo and Icon design</li> <li>Expert in Adobe Photoshop and Illustrator</li> <li>HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Material Design, jQuery</li> <li>Familiar with Angular, Node.JS and Spring Boot</li> <li>REST API, SQL and NoSQL database</li> <li>Good understanding in MVC and Responsive</li> </ul>
IT Operation	Intermediate	<ul> <li>Design</li> <li>Chart and Graph using D3.js and SVG</li> <li>Cloud Hosting using Digital Ocean</li> <li>Experience with version controller like         SourceTree, GitHub and GitLab.     </li> <li>Advance knowledge in many Operating System         like Windows, Linux and Mac.     </li> <li>Data Center Infrastructure and Virtual Machines</li> <li>Servers, Network, Storage and Backup         Equipment Installation and Configuration.     </li> </ul>

iOS App	Beginner	Experienced in Swift programming Xcode IDE
Development		Setting Layout for multiple screen size devices

Kindly visit rezzadanial.com for more details about my skills.

### **REFERENCES**

## 1) Anas Repin

• **Relation:** Intern Supervisor

• Senior System Engineer at Novatis Resources Sdn. Bhd.

• Contact: 018 3799660 / anas@novatis.com.my

## 2) Dr. Shahniza Binti Kamal Bashah

• Relation: Lecturer at UiTM Shah Alam

• Contact: 019 212 2622 / shahniza@tmsk.uitm.edu.my

## 3) Hj. Khalidah Binti Abdul Karim

• Relation: Previous Employer

• Chairman of Pusat eRezeki Shah Alam

• Former Chief Financial Officer at Bank Negara Malaysia

• Contact: 012 218 6655